Investigate database pulling using WHERE instead of the while loop

Fix support for name changes




Implement clear image that will reset signature to color sig
fix non animating gifs
How do to transparency gifs: make master png that keeps adding layers and copy over the master with the new layer before saving
$_SERVER['PHP_AUTH_USER']

ribbons(hellcat padder, 10k personality club, clan hopper)
Clan hopper WOTCS API http://clanapi-wotcs-eu.herokuapp.com/players/PLAYERID/changes
Commitment issues: 3 clans over the course of 3 months
Identity Crisis: been in the same clan twice
Marked for death: been in a shitty clan